(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T16:35:54.456992",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
最近行ったのよ、カラオケ。
I went to karaoke recently.
なんかさ、2時間で解散って思うじゃん？
You'd think it wraps up in two hours, right?
そっからなのよ。
That's when it really starts!
いろんなことできるわけ。
You can do all sorts of things.
やばいぞ。
It's insane.
うまい！
Awesome!
PLAY! NEW (X). X PARK.
Xパーク最高。
X PARK is the best!
ジョイサウンドX1
JOYSOUND X1
ふくや
Fukuya
明太子が
Mentaiko...
切子？姫？
Kireko? Hime?
明太子が生まれ変わる新しい技を生み出しました！
has been reborn with a brand-new technique!
行きます！
Here we go!
ふくやの明太子から生まれためんチーズシリーズ！
The Men Cheese series born from Fukuya's mentaiko!
ピリリな味わい、マコも大好き！
A spicy kick, Mako loves it too!
詳しくはWebで！
Check the web for details!
だって僕は星だから
Because I'm a star,
stellar stellar
きっと君はもう気付いていた
I'm sure you've already noticed,
僕の心の奥で描いた
what I drew deep inside my heart.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024 SPECTRA OF NOVA - FUKUOKA SUNPALACE
Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 "Spectra of Nova" - Fukuoka Sunpalace (Dec 28)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
受注生産グッズ 1 Essentials Pack
Made-to-Order Goods 1: Essentials Pack (Light Stick, T-shirt, Towel, Bag Tag)
受注生産グッズ 2
Made-to-Order Goods 2: Light Stick, T-Shirt, Towel, Ring Light
受注生産グッズ 3
Made-to-Order Goods 3: Long-Sleeve T-Shirt, Shoulder Bag, Socks
受注生産グッズ 4
Made-to-Order Goods 4: Pouch Set, Keychain
受注生産グッズ 5
Made-to-Order Goods 5: Acrylic Stand, Tapestry
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention / 声出し応援OKです
Attention / Cheering loudly is OK
本日は
Today,
星街すいせいライブツアー2020 スペクトラ・オブ・ノヴァにご来場いただきありがとうございます。
Thank you for attending Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2020 SPECTRUM NOVA.
星街すいせいです。
This is Hoshimachi Suisei.
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくためにいくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the concert until the end, I have a few announcements.
いい返事。
Great response.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of photography, recording, or filming equipment during the show is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
Should you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify nearby staff.
会場内でのモッシュ・ダイブ・ステージにものを投げ込む
Mosh pits, stage diving, throwing objects onto the stage,
ほかのみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止となっております。
and any behavior that inconveniences others or disrupts the performance is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください。
Please follow the rules and enjoy the show.
いい返事。
Good response.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合がございます。
and audience seats may appear in the footage.
これら映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますのであらかじめご了承ください。
Please note that these images and videos may be used for promotional purposes.
元気。
Full of energy.
また、ライブのハッシュタグはかけめぐるほしまちです。
Also, the live show's hashtag is #KakemeguruHoshimachi.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください。
Please use the hashtag to get everyone hyped up.
遂に……
Finally...
それでは、開演までもう少しです。みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！
Well then, the show is about to start. Let's all get hyped up together!
イエーイ！またあとで！
Yay! See you soon!
Are you ready?
白いカーテンのsway
The sway of white curtains,
似たような朝のようで
Like a familiar morning,
まるで違う 交差する星彩
Yet completely different, intersecting starlight.
新しく目覚める “thinking to myself”
Waking up anew, "thinking to myself".
定型文のstoryteller
A storyteller of clichés,
micは渡しちゃ駄目圏
The mic is off-limits to hand over.
安全圏のobserver error
An observer error in the safety zone.
何を信じる？
What do you believe in?
oh, oh, 眩しくて
Oh, oh, so dazzling,
逸らした初期衝動
The initial impulse I looked away from.
今追随して
Now following after it.
空性の愛の歌ばかりで
Filled only with hollow love songs,
もう聞き飽きてきたでしょ
You're tired of hearing them by now, right?
blackout流星
Blackout shooting star,
knock down寸前
Right on the verge of a knockdown.
退屈してんじゃない？？
Aren't you getting bored?
“I’m ready to dawn”
"I'm ready to dawn"
千載一遇のnew senseで想像
Imagining with a once-in-a-lifetime new sense,
光速のsympathyで
With light-speed sympathy.
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
直観主義のinnocenceで創造
Creating with intuition-based innocence,
奇跡も世界も自分次第で！
Miracles and the world depend entirely on you!
start to know, 革命の狼煙は
Start to know, the signal fire of revolution is
start to go, 変化を恐れない覚悟さ
Start to go, the resolve not to fear change.
渇いた 大地を駆ける唯一の光
The sole light running across the parched earth.
変わりたい・変えたいの連鎖が
The chain of wanting to change and wanting to change things
剥き出しの魂を焚き付ける
Ignites our bare souls.
6000万年に一度きりのsurpriseで
With a once-in-60-million-years surprise,
ドラマティックなkissにしよう
Let's make it a dramatic kiss.
Encount!
星が揺らいで 夢を見ている
Stars are swaying, having a dream.
焦がれたその音が待っているの
The sound I yearned for is waiting.
キラめくカラー 秘めてる日々に
In days hiding sparkling colors,
伝えるこのメロディ
I convey this melody.
窓から覗いた 雨の降る街並みを
Peering out the window at the rainy cityscape,
弾ける音だから
because it's a bursting sound,
ポケットに詰め込んで
packing it into my pocket—
Let’s dance now
君の好きな
The party song you love
ちょっとcoolでpopな party song
(somewhat cool and pop)
キラチューンのステップに乗せて
Riding on the steps of a killer tune,
魔法のような
like magic,
もっとvivid, passion, shiny ray
(more vivid, passion, shiny ray)
ライトが私を照らしている
the lights are shining upon me.
星を紡いで 夢を描くよ
Weaving the stars, painting a dream.
焦がれたその声が呼んでいるの
The voice I yearned for is calling.
キラめくカラー まといった君に
To you, draped in sparkling colors,
届けるこのメロディ
I deliver this melody.
このままじゃね 終われない
It can't end just like this—
終わらない
(It won't end)
Specialなstage 踊り明かすの
Dancing the night away on a special stage!
明かそう
(Let's dance)
このまま じっとしていられない
I can't just stay still like this—
そうさせない
(I won't let you)
走り出そうよ 明日は晴れるから
Let's run forth, because tomorrow will be clear.
まだ目が覚めない カーテンを開けても
My eyes still aren't open, even opening the curtains,
憂鬱そうだって コメットが流れたら
even if it looks gloomy, once Comet flows by—
Let’s show now
いつも着てた
The girly style you always wore
ちょっとtrend baseな girly style
(a somewhat trend-based girly style)
ショーウィンドウの服 着替えて
changing clothes in the storefront window,
魔法のような
like magic,
もっとcoolでpopな party time
(more cool and pop party time)
ドレスがふわりっとして ひるがえる
my dress flutters and swirls.
満天の星空にほら 浮かべてみて 明日のビジョン
Look, floating tomorrow's vision in the starry sky—
そこで見える そこで見えるなら もっと飛べるよ
if you can see it there, if you can see it, you can fly higher!
満開の笑顔ならほら 歌ってみて このドキドキ
Look, with full blossoms of smiles, try singing this heart-pounding tune—
そこ会える そこ会えるから だってきっと 世界は変わるから！
because you can meet there, because you can meet there, surely the world will change!
明日は晴れるから
Because tomorrow will be clear.
星を紡いで 夢を描くよ
Weaving the stars, painting a dream.
焦がれたその声が呼んでいるの
The voice I yearned for is calling.
キラめくカラー まといった君に
To you, draped in sparkling colors,
届けるこのメロディ
I deliver this melody.
このままじゃね 終われない
It can't end just like this—
終わらない
(It won't end)
Specialなstage 踊り明かすの
Dancing the night away on a special stage!
明かそう
(Let's dance)
このまま じっとしていられない
I can't just stay still like this—
そうさせない
(I won't let you)
走り出そうよ 世界は変わるから
Let's run forth, because the world will change!
La la lalalalalalala
Lalalalala
明日は晴れるから
Because tomorrow will be clear.
音の隙間で 膨らんだ成長
Swelling in the gaps of sound, growth
ガラガラ透けた 賑わいなんてさ
A bustling crowd that was rattling and transparent—
どんな言葉にも ちょっと誤りがあった
Every word had a slight mistake in it.
もう何にも言わずに あそこへ
Without saying anything else, heading there.
どうでもいい朝に 馴れすぎて
Too used to indifferent mornings,
傘を持ってない 借りてた未来
a borrowed future with no umbrella in hand.
かじけず かわしけず からから街行く
Without freezing, without dodging, the parched city walks on—
そのもの
that very thing.
ねえねえ 一人だ かかげたのは maybe
Hey hey, being alone, what I held up was maybe
Rainy day 濡れたネオン街に
Rainy day, on the drenched neon streets,
泣き出したんだ セイシュンの
shedding tears of youth,
なんて締めだったっけ
what kind of ending was that again?
今 君に 会いたい と涙
Now, tears wishing to meet you
こらえて
holding them back,
さよなら さよならなんだって
saying "farewell, farewell"—
認め たくないけど
though I don't want to admit it,
雨上がりの この世界が
this post-rain world
眩しいから
is so dazzling,
もう 帰れない 振り返らない
I can no longer go back, I won't look back.
思い出とともに 新しい
Together with my memories, blowing into
風に 吹かれなれ
a new wind—
そして また君に 会いたいと
and wanting to meet you once more,
願い かけていく
casting a wish as I go on.
初めての場所で やっと見つけた
Finally finding it in an unfamiliar place,
力任せ それでよかった
putting all my strength into it, and that was fine.
泣いて 泣いて 泣いて なんて残った
Crying, crying, crying, what was left?
使い捨ての ドラマじゃしたくないな
I don't want it to be a disposable drama.
謙遜 興奮の
Modest, excited,
センチメンタル公園
sentimental park,
真っ白な煙に 吹かれながら
drifting in the white smoke,
歌う
singing.
救いもない ドマイこと
With no salvation, a clumsy thing—
ねえねえ 一人だ 昨日のさみしさは
Hey hey, being alone, yesterday's loneliness
Maybe Rainy day
すべてを 脱ぎ捨ててゆく
Shedding everything away,
星のように光るみたいに
shining like stars.
だって僕 は 星だから
'Cause I am a star,
stellar stellar
きっと君は もう 気づいていた
I'm sure you had already noticed,
ぼくの心の奥で描いた
drawn deep within my heart—
それがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
a cliché monologue I'll now tell you.
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There was always a word I couldn't say,
壊せない壁があったんだずっとさ
and an unbreakable wall that stood in my way.
ふと香り立つ朝の匂いが
The scent of morning gently rising
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
was so hopelessly hateful to me.
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていた
Hugging my knees, trembling in the corner of my room...
太陽なんかいらないから
I don't need a sun,
明けなまいでいて──
please, just don't let the dawn break.
その手を伸ばして誰かに届くように
Reach out your hand so it touches someone,
僕だって君と同じ特別なんかじゃないから
'cause I'm not special, just like you.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar,
ありったけの輝きで今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まない
with all the brilliance I have. Tonight, the music won't ever, ever stop.
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
isn't some waiting Cinderella...
迎えに行く王子様だ
I am the prince coming to greet her.
だって僕は星だから
'Cause I am a star,
なんてありふれた話なんだ
or so the common story goes.
理想だけ書き連ねていたノートの隅に眠るほんのワンシーンだ──
Just a single scene sleeping in a notebook where I wrote down only ideals.
きっとあの星も泣いてるんだ
I'm sure even that star is crying.
明日なんか来ないままでいて──
Please, just stay without tomorrow ever coming.
その手を伸ばして誰かに届くように
Reach out your hand so it touches someone.
本当に大切なものは目に見えないみたいなんだ
The truly precious things seem invisible.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar,
ありのまま考えないで今宵音楽はきっときっと止まない
thinking as I am, tonight, the music surely won't, won't ever stop.
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to be
あかぬけないヒロインじゃないさ
isn't a helpless heroine...
救いに行くヒーローだ
I am the hero going to save her.
夢見がちなオートギバナシ オートギバナシ
A dreamy fairytale, a fairytale.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar,
ありったけの輝きで今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まない
with all the brilliance I have. Tonight, the music won't ever, ever stop.
そうさ僕は愛を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to love, stellar stellar,
世界、宇宙の真ん中で今宵音楽はきっときっと止まない
right in the middle of the world and the universe. Tonight, the music won't, won't ever stop.
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
isn't some waiting Cinderella...
迎えに行く王子様だ
I am the prince coming to greet her.
だって僕は星だから
'Cause I am a star,
そうさ僕は星だった
that's right, I was a star.
stellar stellar
銀河越しの輝きじゃつまんない
Like a solitary star in the Milky Way,
飛び出すの外なる果てつヘブン
flying out of this world straight to heaven.
目を逸らすの見つめてたよね
You were watching me turn my eyes away, weren't you?
You will align your ray
踏み出した絶望の牢獄脱ぎ捨ててGet out and take
Dumping out all my sorrow, let's update it,
希望の絶望を自分次第で
hoping to crush my helplessness.
さあ次の幕開けをキズにしよう
Let's make it a destiny.
Ah, 空に見上げた
Ah, I gazed at the sky,
眩しすぎるだけじゃ物足りないから
far too bright and dazzling.
偶然じゃない必然のNew senseでさ
It's not just a coincidence,
ポースアップのシンパシーで
getting close with your sympathy.
直感主義のイノセンスでさ
Intuitive, innocent desire,
狭間の世界も自分次第でね
even this world belongs to me.
初の囲い込みの呪いは
That's right, the menace of the beginning
さあどうさ変化を恐れない覚悟さ
is something I don't even fear anymore,
かき消して大地を抱けよいつの日のでりー
I want it to change.
What do you need? What do you take?
望むの場所は何処へ
Where is the place to go?
銀河越しの輝きじゃ
Shining beyond the Milky Way,
つまんない
it's just so boring.
飛び出すの外なる果てツヘブン
Jumping out of this world straight to heaven,
目を逸らすの見つめてたよね
you've been looking away, haven't you?
You will align your ray
踏み出した絶望の牢獄脱ぎ捨ててGet out and take
Dumping out all my sorrow, let's update it,
希望の絶望を自分次第で
hoping to crush my helplessness.
さあ次の幕開けをキズにしよう
Let's make it a destiny.
Ah, 空に見上げた
Ah, I gazed at the sky,
眩しすぎるだけじゃ物足りないから
far too bright and dazzling.
偶然じゃない必然のNew senseでさ
It's not just a coincidence,
ポースアップのシンパシーで
getting close with your sympathy.
直感主義のイノセンスでさ
Intuitive, innocent desire,
狭間の世界も自分次第でね
even this world belongs to me.
初の囲い込みの呪いは
That's right, the menace of the beginning
さあどうさ変化を恐れない覚悟さ
is something I don't even fear anymore,
かき消して大地を抱けよいつの日のでりー
I want it to change.
What do you need? What do you take?
望むの場所は何処へ
Where is the place to go?
こんばんは！
Good evening!
いやー、暑いですね福岡も！
Man, it's so hot here in Fukuoka!
元気ですかー！？
Are you doing well?!
彗星のごとく現れたスターの原石！バーチャルアイドルの星街すいせいです！
The diamond in the rough, appearing like a comet! I'm Hoshimachi Suisei, the virtual idol!
すいちゃんはー！
Sui-chan is—!
きゅーーん！
So cute!
ためてみた、今日は。
I held it in today.
これでためてみた。
I held it in with this.
はい、星街すいせいライブツアー2024「Spectra of Nova」へようこそー！
Welcome to Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 'Spectra of Nova'!
なんとツアーもついに最後の場所となってしまいました……くぅー！
And the tour has finally reached its final stop... Ugh!
そうなんですよ、ええ、埼玉県
That's right, yes, Saitama,
福岡と来て、福岡皆さん、今日が最後なんです！
coming through Fukuoka, and Fukuoka everyone, today is the very last stop!
最後にこれる皆さん！
To everyone who could make it to the end!
こんにちはー！
Helloー!
ちょっと絶妙か、絶妙なMCか。
That's a bit exquisite, or rather, an exquisite MC.
はい、えー先日も発表したんですけども、あの、ライブツアー一旦福岡で終わりつつ、
Right, well, I announced it the other day as well, but while the live tour is temporarily wrapping up in Fukuoka,
あの武道館のライブが実は控え…
the Budokan live is actually coming up...
すごくないですか、皆さん。
Isn't that amazing, everyone?
すごいよね。
It's amazing, right?
いや、本当にそうなんですよね、すごい。ほんで新しいアルバムが出ちゃったりなんだり…
Yeah, really, that's how it is, amazing. And then a new album comes out and whatnot...
そう、さっき言ってたね、Wake Upも新しいサードアルバムにあの入る曲なんですけれども、
Right, as I mentioned earlier, 'Wake Up' is also a song that will be included in the new third album,
いっぱいね、聴いてほしいから、買ってほしいなぁ。
so I want you to listen to it a lot, and I hope you'll buy it.
買った？
You bought it?
もう予約してくれてる人いっぱい！ありがとうございます。
So many people have already pre-ordered it! Thank you so much.
そして今回も前回と同じく、バンドメンバーの皆さんを引き連れております。みんな！
And this time, just like last time, I'm joined by the band members. Everyone!
えー、私、あのさっきまで実は、あの白賢のね控え室にお邪魔して、ギリギリまで
Um, actually, until just a moment ago, I was visiting the dressing room of Shiraishi-ken, and right up until the very last minute,
ルービックキューブやってた。
I was doing Rubik's cubes.
で、なんかそれでね、あ、かわいい？そうだよね、かわいいからいいか。
And, you know, because of that—ah, cute? That's right, since it's cute, that's fine.
それでね、ルービックキューブが下手すぎて、あのフーダにね「ここはこうして、こう回して、そしたらこうだよ」って言われて
And you know, I was so bad at Rubik's cubes that Huuda told me, 'Here you do it like this, turn it like this, and then it's like this,' and
「ええ、やめて！蛙化しちゃうじゃん！これから歌うんでしょ？」って言われました。
I was like, 'Wait, stop! You're going to give me the ick! You're going to sing from now on, right?'
いいからいいか！
Well, whatever, that's fine!
ということで、そんな可愛いすいちゃんを思う存分見れる推しカメラがあります。
With that said, we have an oshi-camera where you can fully enjoy such a cute Sui-chan.
そう、この推しカメラは、あのここに残念ながら来られなかった配信の皆さんの特権です！
Yes, this oshi-camera is a privilege for everyone watching the stream who unfortunately couldn't be here!
さあ、見てるよ、ありがとう。コメントも読んどこうかな、こうほらへんに、なんか宙に浮いてるコメントがね、うん。
Now then, I see you, thank you. Let me read some comments too, around here, floating in the air, yeah.
「いぇーい」「やったぜ」「見えてんで」「釣り席」「うぇーい」「俺らの特権えー」言うてますね。
'Yay', 'Awesome', 'I can see you', 'Fishing seat', 'Yay', 'Our privilege, eh', they're saying.
そしてなんと、えー、韓国でのライブビューイングも行なっています。みんな一緒にアニョハセヨー！
And what's more, um, we are also holding a live viewing in Korea. Everyone together, Annyeonghaseyo!
いやこれ感動するでしょ、韓国の皆さん。「え、今俺たちに向けて言うた？」つって。
Man, this is touching, right, everyone in Korea. 'Eh, did she just say that toward us?' they're saying.
嬉しいですね、いろんなね、世界の方々が観てくださってると。
I'm so happy that people from all over the world are watching.
え、ちなみに今日、海外から来ましたってこと、
Um, by the way, today, anyone who came from overseas—
人？
people?
もう一回、海外から来たって人。
Once more, people who came from overseas.
うわ、すごいいっぱいいるじゃん！すごくない？
Whoa, there are so many of you! Isn't that amazing?
え、あの福岡から来ましたって人。
Um, people who came from Fukuoka—
え、福岡県民ですって人。
Um, people who are Fukuoka residents—
え、多くね！？え、こんなにいるの福岡県民、すごくね？
Eh, there's so many?! Eh, are there really this many Fukuoka residents? Isn't that crazy?
いるよって言った誰か。
Someone said 'We're here!'
えーと、じゃあ最後に福岡県民でも海外の人でもない人。
Um, well then, lastly, people who are neither Fukuoka residents nor from overseas.
じゃあ結構なんかこう半々ぐらいなんだね。
Well, it's about fifty-fifty, huh.
っていうことで、えーライブの感想はハッシュタグかけめぐ星街でたくさんポスト…
So, um, please share your thoughts on the live a lot using the hashtag #KakeMeguHoshimachi and post...
台本いつまでポストなんだっけ？ツイートだよよね！
Wait, until when is it 'post' in the script? It's 'tweet'!
ツイートだよよね！
It's 'tweet'!
ツイートしてくださってことで
Because you tweeted about it,
今回はスマホを持ってきました。
I brought my smartphone with me this time.
スマホでね、ちょっとね、Twitterで、
On my smartphone, I want to Twitter—
ツイートをね、
well, look at tweets—
エゴサしてみたいなって思ってるんです。
I want to ego-search them a bit.
ちょっとMCの時間カツカツなんだけど、私しゃべりすぎて。
My MC time is a bit tight because I talk too much.
えっと、なになに？星まち彗星 210円。
Uh, what's this? Hoshimachi Suisei, 210 yen.
なになに？
What's this?
なんか、え、これ何駅？何駅でこうなってたの？
Wait, what station is this? What station was like this?
あ、博多駅なんだ。博多駅で
Ah, it's Hakata Station. At Hakata Station,
星まち彗星の、え、ライブ会場の最寄り駅まで210円ですっていうのがすごい分かりやすく張り紙が貼ってあったんだよね。
there was a very clear sign saying "210 yen to the nearest station of Hoshimachi Suisei's live venue."
は、貼ったよ？
I-I pasted it?
お前が貼ったの？
Did you paste it?
あ、買ったよか。買ったよね。
Ah, you bought it. You bought it, right?
あと、あの、我らがローソンの、フクヤさんが、なんかどっから明太子売ってって聞いた。
Also, Fukuya at Lawson—I heard they started selling mentaiko from somewhere.
買った？
Did you buy it?
買っ買ってくれました？
絶対に全員買いなさい。
Absolutely everyone must buy it.
本当に美味しいから、なんかね、その空港のところとか、なんかね、地下街の店とか、いろんなところで、
It's really delicious. At places like the airport, or underground shops, in various places,
「福岡の皆様ようこそ福岡へ」って書いてあるの。
it says, "Welcome to Fukuoka, everyone from Fukuoka."
すごくない？
Isn't that amazing?
見に行ってくださいね。
Go check it out, okay?
はい、えーっと、巻いてくださいというね、ジェスチャーが出ましたので、巻いてまいりますよ。
Yes, um, I got a gesture to wrap it up, so I'll wrap it up.
えー無料チラ見せについて、YouTubeTikTokでご覧の方々はここまでです。
Um, regarding the free sneak peek, for those watching on YouTube and TikTok, that's it for now.
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい皆さんは概要欄から配信サイトへ行ってチケットを買ってください。
For everyone who wants to keep having fun together, please go to the streaming site from the description and buy a ticket.
みんなもう一回、えーを、もう一回えーをください。せーの。
Everyone, give me another 'E'. Ready, go!
代わりにね、言っときましょう。はい。
I'll say it instead. Yes.
それでは次の曲は、何の曲が来るのかな？
Now, what song will come next?
お楽しみにお楽しみ！
Look forward to it!
無料パートは終了いたしましたご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.